iadvize.com 2015-10-28

# iAdvize Privacy policy: data and cookies

**1\. Introduction**

iAdvize is committed to the responsible use of information and protecting individual privacy rights on iadvize.com. We want to inform our visitors about which data iAdvize collects and how it is used. You are entitled to review your personal information and to require that this data is deleted. The survey, handling and use of data is carried out in accordance with the data protection laws of the country where the centre which is responsible for handling the data is located. We take the necessary measures to ensure this.

The iAdvize SAS (hereinafter referred to as “iAdvize” or “We”) owns and manages iadvize.com (the “Website”) and services provided by the iAdvize brand. iAdvize respects the privacy of its users and protects their personal data. iAdvize respects the protection of  personal data of its software users and informs these users what information will be processed. Accepting the Terms and Conditions for the use of all iAdvize products or deciding to use iAdvize products and services is equated with the acceptance of the Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy of these services.

**2\. Your data**

In compliance with the code issued by the Information Commissioner under section 51 of the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA), the user is hereby informed that iAdvize processes personal data in order to provide its service. Personal data and user information is collected in order to ensure registration and access to the iAdvize-service. When you sign up for the use of iAdvize services, iadvize.com asks you to provide personal contact information such as your name, company name, address, telephone number and email address. When you purchase the service, you are asked to provide  information about your credit-worthiness and when you make the final payment such as the invoice recipient’s name and address, their credit card number.

This personal information will only be used to answer your questions more accurately and to provide a better service.

_2.1 What information do we collect about you?_

iAdvize guarantees that its data processing is compliant with the Data Protection Act. The  use of personal data and user information is used to improve the service and product. iAdvize will not disclose information or personal information to third parties for sales or marketing reasons.

iAdvize reserves the right to use the user’s provided data to send its own special offers and directly contact the user. In processing your order, we may send your details to, and also use information from credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.  With the exception of the above situations iAdvize will never publish or disclose information about users.

The user may at any time request information about his or her personal data saved by iAdvize. In addition, the user has the right to revoke the iAdvize’s authorization to collect, process and use personal data.

_2.2 How will we use the information about you?_

The company collects data from iAdvize customers in order to provide the requested service. For example, when you filled out the online form to send an email, iAdvize will use this information to contact you about your interest in our services.

The company is entitled to use the data about iAdvize customers for marketing purposes. iadvize.com may use the information you provide to contact you in order to discuss your interests in our services and to send you information about iAdvize or its partners, such as special offers and events.

Credit card information may only be used to verify the credit-worthiness of prospective clients and to charge for the provided services. The iAdvize user is the person who is  exclusively responsible for the way in which iAdvize is installed. It is the user’s responsibility to use web analytics tools in compliance with data protection regulations.

**3\. Cookies**

For a simple and practical use of company websites, iadvize.com uses cookies. If you visit one of the iadvize.com websites, the company’s servers send a cookie to your computer.   Cookies as such do not personally identify you. They merely recognize your browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to the company – for example, by subscribing to the newsletter, or by opening an account and filling out an online form (to get in contact or register for a 14-day trial) – you remain anonymous for iadvize.com.

iadvize.com uses session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are only active during an online session. They are deleted from your computer when you close your browser or shut down your computer. Persistent cookies are stored on your computer even after your browser or computer are shut down.

For further information, visit <http://www.aboutcookies.org.uk/>

If you have identified yourself on iadvize.com, iAdvize will use session cookies which contain encrypted information to enable the system to clearly identify you, as long as you are registered. Each time you log in to one of the iAdvize services, a session cookie with a specific ID associated with your account is placed in your browser. With the help of these session cookies, the company is able to recognize you when you are logged in to one of the services, and can process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies are necessary for the use of services.

The company also uses persistent cookies which can only be read and used by iadvize.com  to identify browsers that have already visited the company websites. When you buy services or provide the company with certain personal data, you will be assigned a specific ID. This specific ID is connected to a persistent cookie which the company places on your Web browser. The company pays special attention to the security and privacy of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, account numbers and passwords are not stored in persistent cookies. If you set your browser not to accept cookies on your browser, you can continue to use the full range of iadvize.com features, but not all our services. Persistent cookies are stored for one year maximum.

**4\. Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, small pieces of data which are stored on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there.

If the IP anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP address will be shortened within Member States of the European Union or signatories of the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases is the complete IP address transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. The IP-anonymisation is active on this site. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity and providing other website and internet related services to the website operator.

The IP address which Google Analytics gets from your browser is not associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, we would point out that in this case, you will not be able to use all the features of this website. You can also prevent the data about your use of the website with cookies (including your IP address) from being collected and processed by Google. All you have to do is download and install the browser plugin available here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

**5\. Security**

iAdvize has taken strong security measures to protect customer data against unauthorized access. The security measures taken ensure the security of user data. iAdvize’s highest priority is to protect user data. However, the security of data transmission over the Internet can not be 100 percent guaranteed.

All iAdvize servers are located in hosting facilities secured by a firewall, they are on the cutting edge of technology and are subject to a full-time supervision by the facility. iAdvize is able to monitor the system 24 hours a day and 7 days a week, so it can respond to problems immediately. The user data is distributed between two data centers and a backup is saved every 24 hours. The user is aware that iAdvize can only guarantee the highest level of privacy if the user keeps his or her login information safe. This login information enables the user to access his or her data. The user, and not iAdvize, is responsible for the content and consequences of his or her chat conversations.

**6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage. The continued use of iAdvize services is deemed as acceptance of changes made to the Privacy Policy. This privacy policy was last updated on 23 August 2013.

**7\. Terms and Conditions**

By using the iAdvize products and services, the user accepts the terms and conditions, which are available at:

<http://www.iadvize.com/terms_of_use_iadvize.html>

**8\. Legal Notices**

iAdvize constantly checks and updates the information on its website. Despite all efforts, data may meanwhile have changed. Therefore, we can not be accountable nor provide the guarantee that the information shared on our website is up to date, correct and complete. Our website also contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites, you should read their own privacy policies. Furthermore iAdvize reserves the right to make changes or additions to the information provided.

**9\. Contact**

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:

By email: [contact-uk@iadvize.com](mailto:kontakt@iadvize.com)

Or write to us at:

iAdvize SAS

2ter Quai François Mitterrand,

44200 Nantes

France
